Bart Cusick
213 Artesian Dr.
Garner NC, 27529
bartcusick@hotmail.com

Cell Phone: (919)-673-4578

Online Portfolio: www.bartcusick.com

# Web Design, Illustration, Animation, Graphic Design, Multi-Media Design

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

A designer with a great imagination. Humorous and open-minded personality has always made it easy to communicate and work with others. Eager to learn, extremely adaptable, and quick to pick up new tasks. Always met customer deadlines. Innovative, imaginative, multimedia oriented, and can draw really cool monsters.

**TARGET JOB** Target Job Title: Studio Designer/ Graphic Designer/ Illustrator

**Alternate Target Job** 

Title:

Designer

**Desired Job Type:** Employee, full time /Contract/Project

**Desired Status:** Full-Time, Part-Time

**Desired Salary:** 40,000+ USD Per Year

**Site Location:** No Preference

## Description of my perfect job:

Creating and designing new, fun, and visually stimulating ways of presenting information through the medium of Web pages, animation, and art. My Ideal job would require Illustration as well as final program or product implementation. Providing a company with the best E-Learning, illustration, web or graphic design possible.

Career Level Experienced (Non-Manager) 15+ years

Date of Availability: Immediately

TARGET COMPANY Category: Internet/E-Commerce

#### Description of my ideal company:

Im looking for a company that is still excited about being in business. A company that is willing to try new things, rewards good work, and allow us to grow together.

**WORK STATUS** US I am authorized to work in this country for any employer.

**EXPERIENCE** 

9/2017 – present Etix Morrisville, NC

**Customer support** 

Help customers and vendors with fast friendly accurate information. Also sell tickets.

3/2002 - Present BartWork!

#### Artist

Custom Artwork, Mural Design and implementation, Painting, Illuistration, Graphic design, Band fliers, T-Shirt Design, Band CD Covers, Comic Book Illustration, Vinyl Signs, Logo Design, Web Design, Company Branding.

Raleigh, NC

7/-06 - 11/13 GCFLearnfree.org Raleigh, NC

# Flash Developer II / Graphic Designer / Interactivity Designer

Create interactive e-learning courses for adult literacy. Create illustration, 3d design, Game design, and graphic design for www.gcfleanfree.org. Create corporate identity and branding materials.

10/-05 – 4/06 Global Knowledge Cary, NC

# **Graphic Designer/ Flash Developer**

Create Graphics and Interactive Flash files for custom E-Learning courses. Clients Included E-labcorp, GSK, Intel, and Schneider Electric.

6/2003 – 2/06 Skinux Cary, NC

#### **Art Director**

Design new and cool animated GUI interfaces for clients such as Kodak, Adobe, x3d,and others. To create artwork for marketing and Corporate branding.

6/2005 – 5/2006 PriceWatch.com San Antonio, TX

#### **Art Director**

Design new and cool animated GUI interfaces for Ooodoggy.com and Pricewatch.com. using Flash MX 2004 pro and html. Use action scripting to create a database driven search engine in flash. To create artwork for marketing and Corporate branding. Create characters for video games and video game ideas, and create movie and music reviews.

5/2003 – 5/2005 Anamel inc. Raleigh, NC

#### Illustrator/ Graphic designer

Create characters and artwork for children books on cd as well as package design. Create illustrations for children books.

12/2002 - 2/2003 Trifolium Raleigh, NC

#### Web Developer

Make all of the changes to UGcorps new web site. Create new business cards, Flash animations, and posters.

12/2001 - 2/2002 McKinney&Silver Raleigh, NC

#### Web Developer

(Contractor) Creating and building online eyeblaster marketing spots, and flash animations for AUDI.

11/2000 - 6/2001 McKinney & Silver. Inc Raleigh, North Carolina

#### Web Designer

(Contractor)Responsible for helping update the McKinney & Silver Flash web site, and creating new interface designs.

2/2000 - 10/2000 She She Me. Inc Raleigh, North Carolina

# Web Designer/Illustrator/Animator/Graphic Designer

She She Me. Inc Raleigh, North Carolina

Web Designer/Illustrator/Animator/Graphic Designer(2/00-10/00)

Responsible for designing, creating the shesheme.com web-site and flash web site, animations, characters, and bi-weekly illustrations.

# **EDUCATION**

12/2003 NC State University US-North Carolina-Raleigh

# **Bachelor's Degree**

3 Years Attended

Museum School of Fine

Arts

US-MA-Boston

## **Bachelor's Degree**

1 year attended.

Massachusetts College of

Art

US-MA-Boston

#### **Bachelor's Degree**

1 semester attended.

Mount Wachusett Community College US-MA-Gardner

# **Bachelor's Degree**

1 year attended.

SKILLS	Skill Name	Skill Level	Last Used	Experience
	Flash Cc	Expert	Currently used	15 years

Illustrator Cc	Expert	Currently used	18 years
InDesign CS6	Expert	Currently used	2 years
After Effects CS6	Expert	Currently used	10 years
Dreamweaver	Intermediate	Currently used	5 years
StoryLine	Expert	Currently used	1 years
ZBrush	Intermediate	Currently used	2 years
3D studio Max	Beginner	2 years ago	1 years
MangaStudio	Expert	1 year ago	1 years
Castemate pro	Intermediate	1 year ago	1 years
Microsoft Word	Expert	Currently used	5 years
Microsoft Excel	Intermediate	Currently used	1 years
PowerPoint	Expert	Currently used	3 years
Swift 3d	Expert	Currently used	1 years

**REFERENCES** Richard Krueger Skinux Owner, Creator

**Phone Number:** (919)-461-8989

Email Address: rkrueger@skinux.com

Reference Type: Professional

**Dean Sheets** GcfLearnfree.org Web developer

**Phone Number:** (919)-621-5858

Email Address: Dean@gcflearnfree.org

Reference Type: Professional

Ana Walle Anamel inc. Owner, Creator

**Phone Number:** (919)-818-7721

Email Address: anamw@aol.com

**Reference Type:** Professional

**Dean Pratt** Skinux Director of Business

**Phone Number:** (919)-601-4505

Email Address: dino@skinux.com

Reference Type: Professional